Inventaris van het Archief van de Raad voor de Scheepvaart (1908) 1909-2010
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- Bijzonder, B.
  - Taakuitvoering, B.2
    - Onderzoek scheepsongevallen, B.2.7
      - Ter documentatie aangeschafte Zeekaarten, B.2.7.3
        - British Admiralty Charts, B.2.7.3.2
          - Miscellaneous, B.2.7.3.2.3
            - Banda Sea, Celebes Sea, Java Sea and Sulu Sea, B.2.7.3.2.3.2
              - 2732: Anchorages in Java, Bali and Lombok, 15th January 1897 (last correction 1957), 3066; blad
              - 2776: Straits between Flores and Lomblen, 23rd October 1912 (revised 1962), 3067; blad
              - 2777: Ujong Pöröla to Ujong Raja, 14th November 1930 (last correcton 1959), 3068; blad
              - 2778: Ujong Raja to Pulo Ilir including Simalur and Banyak Islands, 15th May 1929 (last correction 1958), 3069; blad
              - 2779: Pulo Ilir to Pulo Nyamuk including the off-lying islands from Nias to Siberut, 14th May 1928 (last correction 1958), 3070; blad
              - 2780: Pulo Nyamuk to Benkulen including The Mentawei Islands, 29th June 1927 (last correction 1953), 3071; blad
              - 2781: Benkulen to Sunda Strait including Mega and Telanjang, 1st February 1927 (last correction 1957), 3072; blad
              - 2785: Plans in Sumbawa Island, 10th August 1909 (revised 1962), 3073; blad
              - 2786: Plans on the coast of Halmahera and Vicinity, 14th November 1932 (last correction 1959), 3074; blad
              - 2787: Plans on the coast of Halmahera and Vicinity, 14th November 1932 (last correction 1955), 3075; blad
              - 2788: Halmahera and adjacent islands, 14th November 1932 (last correction 1955), 3076; blad
              - 2948: Udjung Radja to Pulau Delapan - Baai van Tapanuli - Rede Meulaboh - Rede Tapa Tuan - Rede Sibolga, 1st April 1960, 3077; blad
              - 2949: Batang Singkuang to Udjung Sawang Puding, 1st April 1960, 3078; blad
              - 3014: Balik Papan Bay to Pulo Laut, 30th December 1924 (last correction 1959), 3079; blad
              - 3017: Approaches to Pulo Laut, 12th June 1925 (last correction 1956), 3080; blad
              - 3021: Pulo Laut to Tanjong Selatan - Laut Strait, 9th February 1926 (last correction 1957), 3081; blad
              - 3029: Tanjong Seletan to Tanjong Malatayur, 6th September 1910 (last correction 1957), 3082; blad
              - 3030: Koetei Rivier and approaches, 27th October 1945 (last correction 1958), 3083; blad
              - 3031: Bays and anchorages on the east coast of Borneo, 28th February 1899 (last correction 1959), 3084; blad
              - 3044: Tanjong Djontjongang to Tanjong Kasi, 24th June 1899, 3085; blad
              - 3128: Laikang - Malasoro - Pare Pare Bays, 12th January 1900 (last correction 1955), 3086; blad
              - 3161: Tandjung Malatajur to Tandjung Puting, 25th October 1910 (revised 1963), 3087; blad
              - 3193: Cebu Harbour and approaches, 16th September 1966, 3088; blad
              - 3195: Panang to Pulo Motuo, 13th July 1901 (last correction 1957), 3089; blad
              - 3209: Bays and anchorages in Macassar Strait, 27th September 1901 (last correction 1958), 3090; blad
              - 3239: Banda Sea, 3rd November 1944 (revised 1961), 3091; blad
              - 3240: Golf van Tomini, 28th November 1944 (last correction 1958), 3092; blad
              - 3241: Sula Islands and Buru, 14th April 1937 (last correction 1953), 3093; blad
              - 3242: Eastern portion of Ceram Sea, 21st June 1937 (last correction 1958), 3094; blad
              - 3243: Banda Islands to Aroe Islands including Watoebela and Kai Islands, 29th September 1938 (last correction 1956), 3095; blad
              - 3243: Banda Islands to Aroe Islands including Watoebela and Kai Islands, 29th September 1938 (revised 2004), 3096; blad
              - 3244: Eastern Timor and Sermata eilanden - western portion, 28th November 1944 (last correction 1958), 3097; blad
              - 3245: Sermata eilanden - eastern portion and Tanimbar eilanden, 28th November 1944 (last correction 1956), 3098; blad
              - 3246: Pulau-Pulau Aru with part of the south west coast of New Guinea, 28th November 1944 (revised 1962) (last correction 1963), 3099; blad
              - 3248: North west New Guinea and adjacent islands, 28th November 1944 (last correction 1958), 3100; blad
              - 3249: Geelvink Baai, 28th November 1944 (last correction 1960), 3101; blad
              - 3296: Kupang Bay and Roti Strait, 19th September 1916 (last correction 1962), 3102; blad
              - 3311: Anchorages on the north coast of Java, 22nd December 1902 (last correction 1957), 3103; blad
              - 3394: Tanjong Lutuno to Dondo Point, 11th December 1903 (last correction 1958), 3104; blad
              - 3401: Harbours and anchorages in the Kalamian Group, 17th June 1938 (last correction 1954), 3105; blad
              - 3407: Murcielagos Bay, 31st December 1903 (last correction 1955), 3106; blad
              - 3426: Plans on the north coast Mindanao, 8th March 1963, 3107; blad
              - 3440: Anchorages between Sulawesi and New Guinea, 30th June 1905 (revised 1962), 3108; blad
              - 3463: Dumankilas Bay, 17th December 1904 (last correction 1953), 3109; blad
              - 3470: Plans in the southern part of Celebes, 30th April 1906 (last correction 1959), 3110; blad
              - 3475: Plans on the east coast of Luzon, 6th September 1940 (last correction 1961), 3111; blad
              - 3476: Sungai Palembang, 5th August 1949 (revised 1959), 3112; blad
              - 3487: Manila and Cavite anchorages - Manila Harbour, 1st May 1923 (revised 1960), 3113; blad
              - 3559: Anchorages in Luzon, Mindoro and Marinduque, 23rd July 1943, 3114; blad
              - 3616: Tomori Gulf to Salayar Strait including Buton Strait and Gulf of Boni, 6th May 1907 (last correction 1959), 3115; blad
              - 3626: Dumpil Point to Gaya Head, 6th May 1907 (last correction 1953), 3116; blad
              - 3706: Alas Strait and plans, 11th November 1908 (revised 1962), 3117; blad
              - 3756: Linta and Molo Straits, 26th July 1910 (revised 1962), 3118; blad
              - 3726: Straat Bali and plans, 1st June 1909 (last correction 1958), 3119; blad
              - 3728: Marudu Bay, 15th June 1909 (revised 1959), 3120; blad
              - 3697: Lucena anchorage - Pagbilao Bay and Port Laguimanok, 6th July 1908 (last correction 1929), 3121; blad
              - 3805: Luzon Island north of 16º 20' n., 1st December 1925 (revised 1963), 3122; blad
              - 3806: Cabra Island to San Fernando Point, and Diapitan Bay to San Miguel Bay, 28th March 1922 (last correction 1957), 3123; blad
              - 3807: Cuyo Islands to Cabra Island including Mindoro Strait and Sibuyan Sea, 28th August 1923 (last correction 1957), 3124; blad
              - 3808: San Miguel Bay to Leyte Gulf, 30th October 1923 (last correction 1957), 3125; blad
              - 3809: Tagolo Point to Cuyo Islands, 19th August 1924 (last correction 1957), 3126; blad
              - 3810: Leyte Gulf to Mayo Bay, 9th September 1924 (last correction 1957), 3127; blad
              - 3811: Basilan Strait to Kamiguin Island including Tubbataha Reefs, 26th February 1925 (last correction 1957), 3128; blad
              - 3815: Tanao Pass, Legaspi Port and approaches, 13th October 1961, 3129; blad
              - 3817: Tablas Strait with part of Sibuyan Sea, 6th November 1936 (last correction 1956), 3130; blad
              - 3819: Mindoro Strait, 17th June 1938 (last correction 1956), 3131; blad
              - 3820: Cuyo West Pass, 25th November 1938 (last correction 1956), 3132; blad
              - 3821: Cuyo East Pass, 16th February 1939 (last correction 1956), 3133; blad
              - 3822: Sibuyan and Visayan Seas from Tablas to Bantayan Island, 31st March 1936 (last correction 1956), 3134; blad
              - 3823: Visayan and Samar Seas, 5th December 1935 (last correction 1955), 3135; blad
              - 3824: Passages between Panay, Negros and Sebu, 8th October 1936 (last correction 1957), 3136; blad
              - 3825: Camotes Sea with Kanigao Channel, 31st March 1936 (last correction 1957), 3137; blad
              - 3826: Surigao Strait with Leyte Gulf and Hinatuan Passage, 28th September 1936 (last correction 1957), 3138; blad
              - 3827: Western part of Mindanao Sea, 10th July 1939 (last correction 1957), 3139; blad
              - 3840: San Juanico Strait and approaches, 1st July 1935 (last correction 1958), 3140; blad
            - Black Sea, B.2.7.3.2.3.3
              - 1233: Constanta anchorage - Bender Erekli, 30th June 1904 (last correction 1952), 3141; blad
              - 1275: Eregli to Amasra, 11th January 1991, 3142; blad
              - 2206: Odessa Bay and Harbours, 9th March 1887 (last correction 1956), 3143; blad
              - 2231: Cape Kaliakra to Odessa, 16th January 1854 (last correction 1949), 3144; blad
              - 2399: Gulf of Pyrgos - Messemvria to Cape Emineh - Burghaz Bay, 29th December 1855 (last correction 1947), 3145; blad
              - 2399: Gulf of Pyrgos or Burghaz - Messemvria to Cape Emineh - Burghaz Bay, 29th December 1855 (last correction 1956), 3146; blad
              - 3930: Northern approaches to the Bosporus, 24th November 1944 (last correction 1947), 3147; blad
              - 2231: Cape Kaliakra to Odessa, 16th January 1854 (last correction 1931), 3148; blad
            - Caribbean Sea, Gulf of Mexico, B.2.7.3.2.3.4
              - 197: Marigot Harbour to Pointe du Cap, 1st March 1875 (last correction 1958), 3149; blad
              - 254: Montserrat, 1st February 1869 (last correction 1931), 3150; blad
              - 255: Morant Point to Portland Point, 8th March 1963, 3151; blad
              - 257: Ports Morant and Esquivel, Salt River anchorage, 8th May 1959 (last correction 1964), 3152; blad
              - 371: Martinique, 27th April 1863 (last correction 1954), 3153; blad
              - 373: Plans in the Gulf of Campeche, 10th December 1954 (last correction 1957), 3154; blad
              - 373: Plans in the Gulf of Campeche, 10th December 1954 (revised 1987), 3155; blad
              - 374: Punta Zempoala to Punta Coyol, Puerto de Vera Cruz and approaches, Puerto de Tampico, 17th April 1955 (last correction 1956), 3156; blad
              - 374: Punta Coyl to Punta Zempoala, Puerto de Vera Cruz and approaches, Puerto de Tampico, 17th April 1955 (revised 1960) (last correction 1961), 3157; blad
              - 376: Vera Cruz to Tampico, 3rd March 1961, 3158; blad
              - 396: Cabo la Vela to Chagres and Gulf of Panama, 13th October 1892 (last correction 1956), 3159; blad
              - 410: Puerto Sagua la Grande, Bahia de Cardenas, 3rd October 1928 (last correction 1958), 3160; blad
              - 414: Habana Harbour, 4th June 1954 (last correction 1956), 3161; blad
              - 446: Jamaica, 27th October 1880 (revised 1959), 3162; blad
              - 450: Pedro Bank, 1st June 1882 (revised 1959), 3163; blad
              - 454: Port Royal and Kingston Harbours, 18th january 1916 (last correction 1951), 3164; blad
              - 454: Kingston Harbour including Port Royal, 7th October 1960, 3165; blad
              - 456: Port Royal and Kingston Harbours and approaches, 9th March 1876 (last correction 1948), 3166; blad
              - 456: Approaches to Kingston, 9th March 1962, 3167; blad
              - 457: Portland Bight, 27th August 1954 (revised 1963), 3168; blad
              - 467: Bayajibe to Haina, 9th July 1954, 3169; blad
              - 472: Harbours and anchorages in Haiti and the Dominican Republic, 15th September 1896 (last correction 1953), 3170; blad
              - 472: Mona Passage, 12th August 1955 (last correction 1956), 3171; blad
              - 478: Plans in Puerto Rico, 12th February 1954 (last correction 1961), 3172; blad
              - 481: Serpents Mouth including approaches to Caño Macareo, 7th June 1957 (revised 1962), 3173; blad
              - 481: Serpent's Mouth, 19th October 1984, 3174; blad
              - 482: Port of Spain, approaches to Pointe-à-Pierre and Brighton, 8th February 1957, 3175; blad
              - 483: Bocas del Dragon to Serpent's Mouth, 20th December 1957 (revised 1962), 3176; blad
              - 484: Bocas del Dragon, Puerto Cristobal Colon, 22nd July 1935 (last correction 1951), 3177; blad
              - 484: Plans in the Gulf of Paria, 22nd July 1935 (last correction 1956), 3178; blad
              - 486: Jamaica and Pedro Bank, with parts of Cuba and Haïti, 20th December 1866 (last correction 1932), 3179; blad
              - 486: Jamaica and Pedro Bank with parts of Cuba and Haiti, 20th December 1866 (revised 1960), 3180; blad
              - 491: Anchorages in Guadeloupe and adjacent islands, 24th March 1883 (last correction 1937), 3181; blad
              - 493: Approaches to Trinidad, including the Gulf of Paria, 20th December 1957 (revised 1960), 3182; blad
              - 494: Ports and anchorages in Martinique, 14th April 1882 (last correction 1954), 3183; blad
              - 494: Plans in Martinique, 5th October 1956 (last correction 1957), 3184; blad
              - 502: Barbados - Speightstown and approaches to Bridgetown, 13th October 1939 (revised 1963), 3185; blad
              - 697: Dominica, 20th September 1876 (last correction 1938), 3186; blad
              - 703: Plans on the north coast of South America, 17th September 1948 (last correction 1951), 3187; blad
              - 728: Dominica Island - Prince Rupert Bay, 16th June 1873 (last correction 1946), 3188; blad
              - 761: West India Islands and Caribbean Sea - northern sheet, 3rd July 1876 (revised 1960), 3189; blad
              - 762: West India Islands and Caribbean Sea - southern sheet, 22nd July 1913 (last correction 1948), 3190; blad
              - 804: Approaches to Pointe ã Pitre - Ste. Marie anchorage, 15th May 1872 (last correction 1956), 3191; blad
              - 885: Guadeloupe with adjacent islands, 6th March 1882 (last correction 1955), 3192; blad
              - 975: Galveston Bay to Calcasieu Pass, 17th December 1954, 3193; blad
              - 975: Galveston Bay to Calcasieu Pass, 17th December 1954 (revised 1966), 3194; blad
              - 1204: Belize to Cabo Catoche, 18th January 1832 (last correction 1947), 3195; blad
              - 1205: Coast of Yucatan and Campeche Bank, 23rd May 1848 (last correction 1947), 3196; blad
              - 1217: Florida Strait - south part, 31st October 1890 (last correction 1950), 3197; blad
              - 1218: San Juan de Nicaragua to Cabo Gracias, 29th June 1844 (last correction 1947), 3198; blad
              - 1218: San Juan de Nicaragua to Cabo Gracias, 29th June 1844 (last correction 1958), 3199; blad
              - 1219: Cabo Gracias a Dios to Belize, 1st June 1843 (last correction 1948), 3200; blad
              - 1225: Gulf of Campeche, 3rd March 1961, 3201; blad
              - 1266: South-eastern portion of the Bahama Islands, 5th June 1889 (last correction 1955), 3202; blad
              - 1273: St. Lucia, 1st November 1889 (last correction 1960), 3203; blad
              - 1276: Cabo de San Juan de Guia to Punta Galera, 11th August 1944 (last correction 1954), 3204; blad
              - 1277: Punta Galera to Isla Fuerte, 10th August 1945 (last correction 1955), 3205; blad
              - 1299: Panama Canal, 17th September 1922 (last correction 1955), 3206; blad
              - 1299: Panama Canal, 21st June 1957, 3207; blad
              - 1380: Bahia Nipe, 27th July 1901 (last correction 1951), 3208; blad
              - 1452: Nassau Harbour, 1st August 1842 (last correction 1962), 3209; blad
              - 1480: Tobago to Tortuga, 3rd December 1894 (revised 1959), 3210; blad
              - 1489: New Providence, 25th August 1848 (last correction 1954), 3211; blad
              - 1498: Bahia Pozuelos and approaches, 10th August 1945 (last correction 1958), 3212; blad
              - 1519: Entrance to Laguna de Maracaibo, 13th April 1934, 3213; blad
              - 1519: Canal de la Barra de Maracaibo, 7th December 1962 (last correction 1963), 3214; blad
              - 1523: Plans on the coast of Venezuela, 27th March 1953 (last correction 1954), 3215; blad
              - 1529: Golfo de Venezuela, 21st June 1930 (last correction 1955), 3216; blad
              - 1799: Anchorages on the north coast of Panama, 15th June 1927 (last correction 1956), 3217; blad
              - 1963: Anchorages on the coast of Venezuela, 16th April 1925 (last correction 1959), 3218; blad
              - 1966: Tortuga to Cabo La Vela, 3rd December 1894 (revised 1960), 3219; blad
              - 1997: Leeward Islands - Barbuda Island, 1st June 1861 (last correction 1930), 3220; blad
              - 2064: Antigua, 1st October 1954, 3221; blad
              - 2065: St. Johns Harbour to Parham Harbour, 4th June 1954, 3222; blad
              - 2075: Old Bahama Channel to Exuma, 18th August 1851 (revised 1959), 3223; blad
              - 2259: Plans on the coast of Colombia, 23rd September 1938 (last correction 1954), 3224; blad
              - 2259: Plans on the coast of Colombia, 23rd September 1938 (last correction 1955), 3225; blad
              - 2425: River Hueson to False Cape including Morrison and Mosquito Cays, 29th September 1900 (last correction 1946), 3226; blad
              - 2434: Bahia de Cartagena and approaches, 3rd November 1939 (last correction 1955), 3227; blad
              - 2485: Barbados, 26th February 1873 (last correction 1948), 3228; blad
              - 2579: Cuba, 11th February 1907 (last correction 1948), 3229; blad
              - 2600: Mona Passage to Dominica, 19th July 1858 (last correction 1951), 3230; blad
              - 2831: Plans in the Gulf of Mexico, 20th May 1955 (revised 1967), 3231; blad
              - 2853: Mississippi Sound and Mobile Bay, 14th February 1862 (last correction 1948), 3232; blad
              - 2897: Tampa Bay, 22nd December 1933, 3233; blad
              - 2897: Tampa Bay, 22nd December 1933 (revised 1960), 3234; blad
              - 3188: Sabine Pass and Canals to Beaumont and Orange, 7th November 1922 (last correction 1953), 3235; blad
              - 3197: Bahia Nuevitas, 9th September 1901 (last correction 1960), 3236; blad
              - 3224: Terceira and Graciosa, 4th November 1960 (revised 1963), 3237; blad
              - 3290: Livisa and Cabonico Bays, 3rd October 1902 (last correction 1950), 3238; blad
              - 3380: Plans in the Gulf of Mexico, 30th April 1954 (revised 1961), 3239; blad
              - 3382: Mississippi River, the passes to New Orleans, 24th July 1933 (last correction 1933), 3240; blad
              - 3382: Mississippi River from the passes to New Orleans, 24th July 1933 (revised 1962), 3241; blad
              - 3408: Puerto Rico, 2nd April 1904 (last correction 1956), 3242; blad
              - 3450: Ensenada de Mora, 8th October 1904 (last correction 1960), 3243; blad
              - 3473: Santa Cruz del Sur and approaches, 27th January 1905 (last correction 1954), 3244; blad
              - 3689: Eastern part of Haïti to Puerto Rico including Mona Passage, 4th August 1908 (last correction 1951), 3245; blad
              - 3799: Ensenada de Mora to Cayo Anclitas, 21st September 1922 (last correction 1948), 3246; blad
              - 3800: Cayo Anclitas to Puerto Casilda, 5th March 1923 (last correction 1956), 3247; blad
              - 3865: Cuba - eastern sheet, 31st March 1939 (last correction 1948), 3248; blad
              - 3866: Cuba - middle sheet, 7th July 1939 (revised 1962), 3249; blad
              - 3867: Cuba - western sheet, 4th August 1939 (last correction 1962), 3250; blad
              - 3980: Ship Shoal to Brazos Santiago, 28th December 1951 (revised 1967) (last correction 1969), 3251; blad
              - 3981: Cape San Blas to Ship Shoal, 26th June 1953 (revised 1968) (last correction 1969), 3252; blad
              - 3982: Key West to Cape San Blas, 22nd May 1953 (revised 1967), 3253; blad
            - China Sea and Yellow Sea, B.2.7.3.2.3.5
              - 37: Hoihow Bay, 24th February 1880 (last correction 1948), 3254; blad
              - 94: Paracel Islands, 25th June 1885 (last correction 1959), 3255; blad
              - 264: Plans on the east coast of Viet-Nam, 7th October 1955 (last correction 1957), 3256; blad
              - 270: Macclesfield Bank, 15th April 1882 (last correction 1980), 3257; blad
              - 341: Islands south of Lantau, 16th February 1962, 3258; blad
              - 342: Kap Shui Mun to Chuen Pi Channel, 16th February 1962, 3259; blad
              - 343: Kap Shui Mun to Chuen Pi Channel - northern sheet, 16th February 1962, 3260; blad
              - 361: Tambelan Eilanden and Badas Eilanden, 2nd May 1958, 3261; blad
              - 362: Pratas Island (Tung-Sha Tao), 3rd March 1950 (last correction 1951), 3262; blad
              - 380: Taitan Wan, 25th June 1894 (last correction 1954), 3263; blad
              - 769: Sungei Sedili Besar to Kuala Pahang, 4th November 1949 (revised 1960), 3264; blad
              - 770: Kuala Pahang to Trengganu, 28th June 1963, 3265; blad
              - 771: Trengganu to Tumpat, 30th May 1952 (last correction 1956), 3266; blad
              - 857: Kiaochow Bay, 20th January 1865 (revised 1971), 3267; blad
              - 913: Mackau Group to Clifford Islands, 10th December 1906 (last correction 1967), 3268; blad
              - 937: Eastern approaches to Hong Kong, 16th February 1962 (revised 1966), 3269; blad
              - 938: Hong Kong and approaches, 16th February 1962 (revised 1966), 3270; blad
              - 948: Balábac Strait and channels between Borneo and Palawan, 1st August 1870 (last correction 1959), 3271; blad
              - 966: Anchorages in Balambángan and Balábac Islands, 3rd January 1871 (last correction 1956), 3272; blad
              - 967: Palawan Island, 3rd November 1856 (last correction 1957), 3273; blad
              - 1000: Archipel de Poulo Condore, 26th June 1953, 3274; blad
              - 1010: Kulao Cham with entrance to Fai Fo River, 12th October 1868 (last correction 1954), 3275; blad
              - 1015: Plans in Song Sai Gon, 21st August 1959 (revised 1971), 3276; blad
              - 1016: Song Sai Gon, 21st August 1959 (revised 1971) (last correction 1992), 3277; blad
              - 1201: Reefs in China Sea, 23rd October 1888 (last correction 1954), 3278; blad
              - 1255: Kiaochow Bay to Lai Chau Bay, 18th December 1906 (last correction 1965), 3279; blad
              - 1256: Gulfs of Pohai and Liaotung, 1st May 1862 (last correction 1952), 3280; blad
              - 1256: Gulfs of Pohai and Liaotung, 1st May 1862 (last correction 1960), 3281; blad
              - 1258: Approaches to Seoul, 21st May 1907 (last correction 1970), 3282; blad
              - 1259: Pusan and Masan, 26th March 1993, 3283; blad
              - 1261: Approaches to Saigon, 13th November 1959, 3284; blad
              - 1262: Hong Kong to Gulf of Liau-Tung, 24th March 1877 (last correction 1957), 3285; blad
              - 1263: China Sea (general), 30th May 1887 (last correction 1948), 3286; blad
              - 1263: China Sea, 30th May 1887 (last correction 1959), 3287; blad
              - 1263: China Sea, 30th May 1887 (revised 1960), 3288; blad
              - 1270: Approaches to Inch'on, 22nd May 1933 (last correction 1970), 3289; blad
              - 1311: Singapore Strait to Borneo (northern sheet) - Anambas and Natuna eilanden, 27th March 1959, 3290; blad
              - 1312: Singapore Strait to Selat Karimata, 18th February 1994 (last correction 1999), 3291; blad